The 1st Ichi-Hello!
Yes!
Yes, so hello everyone! We are
We are Miyari-Kanjyo!
So cute!
Yes, we are going to decide who is the most knowledgeable member about Ayumi.
How about you two?
How about you two, how is your confidence?
We are from the same place, so we have breathed the same air together since we were little.
I am very confident.
I want to win about human beings with Ayumi every day,
About people?
Yes, I think I can do it.
So, now that we both have confidence, let's do our best.
Let's get started!
Go ahead!
Here is the first question! What TV programs do you watch most often?
What TV shows do you watch most often? Is it difficult? I've heard of it.
I might have. About a year ago.
Since then, he may have changed. He doesn't tell me that he watches this or that.
You never tell me what you watch or what you're into, so I don't think you'd understand.
Shall I write it down? Let's do it!
Late night since I got married. Me too! Me too! What's this? What's this?
But you seem to like it. I have an image of it.
What do you think? Let's see the correct answer. This way.
I thought I should check what's going on in the world. It's a news program.
Indeed. It was updated, wasn't it?
It's on the news, you know.
It's close, isn't it?
Is it close?
But, you know, it all fits.
I like it.
I like it all, but lately, before I go out, when I get up a little early, I turn on the TV and it only has the news on, so I watch that and get ready for makeup.
It's amazing.
I can only watch the news these days.
I still have a long way to go.
I have a lot of work to do. I'll do my best.
Okay, the second question. This way.
What are you into these days?
What I'm into? Oh, that's a tough one. Does everyone seem to know? I don't think so. I think it's pretty difficult.
It's a bit of a hint, but I think it's something that fans would like. I'm sure everyone else is doing it.
I think they do. Everyone is doing it. I think Aoi does a lot of things. A lot? A lot? Every day without fail. Every day?
Maris does it too. Yuukachan does it too. Everyone does it. Everyone does it. Did you write it down? I did. Now, let's open the answers.
I'm into choosing wigs and clothes for online storytelling sessions. I see.
What about Aoi? I misspelled the kanji a little. Makeup research.
I see.
Then, Fancer?
Fancier.
I wear a wig at the end of my talks and in the showrooms.
I often wear a wig at the end of a talk, so I guess it makes my fans happy to see me in a way they don't often get to see.
Okay, let's see the correct answer.
Here is the correct answer.
What I've been into lately is watching my fans.
Oh! Surveillance?
You all know what I'm talking about? Sure, I do. Sure, I do.
Everybody knows about it.
Another word for it is ego search. It was an ego search.
I would search for my name and see what people were tweeting about,
Also, if I posted a story on Instagram, I could see who had viewed it,
It would be recorded, and every five minutes or so, it would be posted. Wow!
That's amazing!
I don't know, like, "You looked at it," or "You sent me a story heart.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Hey, I'm happy for you.
He's so cute.
That was different.
It wasn't the same.
It's different.
No, it wasn't.
But I'm glad you understood Annie so well.
Really?
I'm glad. I'm glad.
I'm so glad.
Third question.
What does X's profile picture say in the "special skills" column?
I think I can do it.
I'm really confident about Yuka.
Was it on the radio when I was in Fukuoka for that campaign?
Didn't we talk about it on the radio?
Maybe I did.
People often ask me what I'm good at.
I'm sure someone has already told you.
Okay, let's see the answers now.
Okay.
What!
Wow!
Saving? Oh, yeah! Maybe! That's for sure!
Saving money, sleeping a lot, makeup.
Makeup. That's the image you have.
Saving money, for sure. What do you think?
Let's take a look. Go ahead.
Saving money.
It's so hard! It's so hard!
Yuko saved the money.
You don't see that word in the specialties.
So it had a strong impact on me.
I was impressed that she wrote "saving" among all the other members.
Aoi's "knead a lot" was written before this special skill in the early days.
In those days, she wrote that "kneading a lot" was her skill.
That's the reason why Aoi will probably continue to be in my head for a long time.
The fourth question is here. What is the first word you want Ki-chan to say now that she can speak?
I want you to say it, I want you to say it, I want you to say it, I want you to say it, I want you to say it, I want you to say it!
Heart-shaped... heart-shaped... I think there's going to be a heart after that word.
Yes, yes...
Yes, yes, yes, yes... I love Ayumi! I love Ayumi! I love Ayumi!
Aren't they all the same? They're all the same. Great. What do you think? Let's see? Let's see.
Here you go.
Tell me you love me. - I love you.
You love it? Yeah.
I don't feel like I'm a mom.
I can't imagine Kin-chan calling me mom.
I'd like you to call me Nenee.
Ayumi? That's right.
I want you to tell me you love me.
And this? That's right.
Yes! I'm so happy!
If I love you, I'm going to save the world.
I'm going to save the world.
Now for the fifth question. Dasan! If you were to share a house with a member, who would you prefer to share it with?
Ayumi, I wonder... I have an image that she likes to keep clean. Yeah, I wonder. I'm not really good at cooking.
Well, maybe someone who cooks for me. I'd like someone who cooks for me. Well, I don't know. Do you have any more tips for me?
Are you being nice? No, I don't know. I was thinking someone who would take care of me. I won. I won. I won. Did you guys call it?
Ready, go! Benon! Yuka.
Why is this Lennon?
You seem to like Lennon, don't you?
You seem to like Lennon.
Lennon looked so maidenly when he dressed up as a man in an online story-telling session. Ayumi.
They took a lot of two-shots when he was dressed as a man.
Lennon said that she cooks for herself, and that she makes and prepares her own food, so I got the image that she might support Ayumi.
It's true that Lennon has a family-oriented image.
That's amazing.
I see.
Yes, I see. How about you, Ao?
I was torn between him and Lennon, but he left his wallet somewhere.
That's right.
So, Yuu-chan is a little more solid in that respect.
A little more. I see.
Then, here is the correct answer.
Well, she's really good at cooking, and she said she also likes to clean the house, so it's Yuuka.
Yay!
I got it!
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
That's the correct answer.
Yeah!
Yes, cooking.
It's important to be good at cooking, and I also thought there must be someone who can clean my room and stuff.
Then I thought Yuka was the only one.
Glad to hear it.
One extra point for Ms. Blue.
Yay!
I didn't say I did it, I didn't guess it!
But I'm so happy!
That's great!
Okay, here's the sixth question.
This is Onishi and Ao, where are you two going on your outing?
Oh!
I think Aoi seems to know a lot about this. Really?
Really? He talks a lot. Oh, really?
I think I might know a little bit, but if I'm wrong, I'm gonna be a little Gavin.
I'll give you a hint. It doesn't really matter if it's fall or not.
No, it doesn't, really, it doesn't. Yes, it does, but you haven't gone to it yet.
Oh, I see... I'll go.
I'm going to the museum, Dreamland, Yuriba.
I'm pretty lost.
Dreamland, I'll have a look. Here's the correct answer.
But Aoi really loves Seiko Omori, so...
Seiko Omori's live performance.
Tell me, I really do.
Why like this?
I'm looking for a place near Tokyo, and now I really want to go.
I've been talking about how I don't think I'll be able to go on this day, right?
I've made the mistake of saying that I'm not going to be able to go to the cat day.
What a compliment!
I'm complimenting you.
The way she cooks... well... the fish eyes...
I have a small face and beautiful eyes.
I have a small face, beautiful eyes, good style, and a good dancer.
I see.
I'm so happy.
You write a lot.
I'm sure you'll say that.
Okay, here's the correct answer.
It's "Meru"!
You have a really cute face and you're always so kind to me.
During lessons, if I don't know how to do something, she tells me what's wrong and tells me what to do.
She always tells me in an easy-to-understand way.
Thank you for everything.
I feel bad saying thank you, don't I?
I see.
Cooking.
You didn't say that.
You didn't.
I said you have a pretty face.
You're going to be a little clumsy, aren't you?
May I?
Yes!
This one goes in.
Aoi said you're beautiful too, even though she praised your looks.
We're the same, so Aoi too, OK.
It's too sweet!
The one by Seiko Omori, right?
It wasn't sweet.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Oh?
Are you a good dancer or not? You're right.
Bingo!
Bingo! That was great.
Yes!
I'm happy to say that all three of you passed.
Passed!
One extra point.
Thank you very much.
Next, the 8th question?
Now Yuka has 3 points
Ao-san also has 3 points, and I have 2 points.
What do you think of the last one?
What is the point?
How many points?
Like 100.
It's okay, it's okay. If Ayumi-ou say so.
The next point is 100 points.
That's great.
I did my best.
Please keep up the good work.
Here is the last one.
What is my first impression of mountain ice cream?
This is your first impression? Since the camp. It's the first time we talked.
Well, here are the first two answers.
Cute, pretty face, cute, white, mature.
They're saying that.
I think they're saying that. Yes, it's true.
She looks mature in the audition video. I should have written "adult-like.
You look like a baby. I see.
Her face is too well-defined. Fashionable.
I'm glad. I see.
My answer is small in stature and cute.
Cute. Cute.
He's cute. He's cute.
He's cute. Here is the correct answer.
It's really transparent from the start.
Really? Really?
I thought she was really transparent.
That's true...
Transparent? White?
Transparent.
White.
Is Yuka right for white?
Yuka, add 100 points.
Yay!
Ten points.
I also thought it was small and cute.
I'm just embarrassed.
You're cute, so be confident.
The final score was 103 points for Yuka, 3 points for Blue, and 2 points for 4.
So, Yuka is the King of Chihara.
The King of Chihara!
Yay!
I'm not good at talking to people like this, so it's great that you know me
I'm so happy to be able to talk to you all!
I'm so happy! So this is King Chihara!
Bye, bye, bye!